Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Good evening.
Kashiage etc.
Yes, I got a lot of "Good evening".
I'm Ginchu.
I'll be signing autographs online to celebrate my solo debut.
Thank you for watching.
And, thank you very much.
Yes, I got a haircut.
It's my first time to show you guys how it moves.
It's a little short.
I'll tell you why I cut it.
I'll tell you later.
I made my solo debut with the song "from about you" on June 28th, and it's already been a month.
It's been a month!
Are you listening to it?
Aren't you tired of it yet?
I'm here today wearing the outfit from the music video.
How fast?
They're listening.
There's more than just this Bout 2.
This month?
4 songs have been released on the EP.
Already a month? Hey, it's early, isn't it?
It's already the end of July.
Wow, that was fast.
People say, "Why are you ripping costumes?
Why do they say that?
It's a costume.
It's torn.It's torn.
It's not my fault it's torn.
Do you want to stay in the archives today? I mean...
Yes.
I think there's an expiration date.
I'll be signing autographs online.
I'm going to call your name at the online signing.
I may be able to write it down.
I'm working on it right now.
I'm doing it now, but I'm at work or something.
I was wondering if there are some of you who are at work
I'm doing it now, but I'm afraid that some of you are at work or can't see it right now.
I'll let you know when it's done.
I'll let you know when the deadline is.
I'll let you know when it expires.
I'll keep it.
Yes, sir.
You're at work or on your way home from work.
I'm watching this while I'm working.
I wonder if it's okay to watch it while you work.
I don't know.
It's amazing that everyone is leaving work.
I wonder if they're going to get mad at me for doing this.
Should I do this already?
It's been so long since I've done an online signing.
I've been doing online signings for so long, I'm forgetting how to do it.
What's going on?
I'll tell you all about it when it's over.
Let's just do it.
I'd better do it.
I'll do it.
All you have to do is pull this.
It's okay.
Can we go?
Can I do it?
I don't have it.I don't have it.
I don't have it.
Guess what?
Hinata Kashiwagi's title at Sony Music is really cool.
What do you mean?
What does my title say at Sony Music?
I'm scared.
Forget it. Let's start.
I don't even know what it says.
I've been here a year.
I've got a lot of them here.
I've already taken a picture of you like this.
I'm signing it.
I'm wearing this red outfit.
And the guy who doesn't drink beer today.
You know...
It's a franchise.
This is a proper franchise.
The franchise is in good standing.
I mean, they're all right, but...
Like this on YouTube.
If I let you do it while drinking at a signing like this...
It's forever.
Okay, I'm going to take a picture of the first one.
Thank you, Daiyuu-san.
Thank you for your comment. You must be Daiyuu since you're doing this.
Thank you very much. Congratulations on your solo debut, Hina-chan!
And your first single EP is great, and I've been playing it on repeat.
I've been following Hinachan for 10 years this year since I was in the 6th grade of elementary school.
You are in the 6th grade of elementary school?
When I was in Ebichu, I didn't have enough money to go to the live only once or twice a year.
But now that I'm a university student, I've saved up enough money to go to live shows once or twice a year.
I'm going to go to see you at various events and live shows from now on.
I will continue to support Hina-chan's activities from now on.
Thank you very much!
She said she's been in elementary school since 6th grade.He said he's been in sixth grade.
He's probably a few years younger than me.
I started shrimping in the sixth grade.
I'll write it down as soon as possible.
Mr. Oyu, can I write it here?
Mr. Oyu.
Yes, this time with your name.
Your signature, your name, and your name and your name and your name and your name and your name and your name and your name and your name.
College students, when you have enough money...
Keep it safe. Don't spend it too much.
Pace yourself.
Mr. Oyu, you're the first one.
Thank you very much.
I'll keep on doing it
Thank you, Mr. Fuji!
Thank you, Fuji-san.
Hinata Kashiwagi Congratulations on your solo debut!
I can't sleep at night because I can't wait to hear you live!
I am looking forward to seeing many more wonderful performances from you! So, thank you very much.
Mr. Fuji
I can't sleep at night, but I appreciate you listening to me and watching mv.
I'm glad.
Mr. Fuji
That's great!
You wrote something with one signature.
I've never done it before, except for love.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Fuji.
Thank you.
I'm glad you wrote it.
He wants me to try writing with my left hand. That's terrible!
I'm really bad at writing with my left hand.
It's a girl, Mio.
Thank you. Congratulations on your solo debut, Hinachan.
I'm encouraged by Hina-chan, who always goes straight ahead in her own way.
I'll support you as much as I can so that you can continue to be a sparkling Hinachan even after you go solo.I will support you as much as I can so that you can continue to be a sparkling Hina-chan even after you go solo.
Thank you, Mio-chan.
I can't believe you're shining so brightly.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Mio-chan.
Of course, there are many of you who got to know me after I went solo.
But basically speaking, there are many of you who have been supporting me since I became a shrimp.
Thank you very much.
Is this how I should do it?
Is this how to do it?
Thank you very much.
Mio.
Everyone said the comments are nice.
They're commenting on it.
They say it's a nice comment.
Everyone's comments are really nice.
I haven't taken any pictures since I cut my hair.
I took more the other day.
Thank you, Ineine!
Thank you, Hinata Kashiwagi!
Congratulations on your solo debut!
Personally, of all the songs included in the album.
Bloom is my personal favorite.
If you have any recommendations for this song from Hinata's point of view, please let us know.
Please let me know!
I'll be supporting you in your solo career as well, so please keep sharing your wonderful voice with us.
Please continue to share your wonderful voice with us!
Thank you, Ineine-san!
Bloom.
Bloom is not so popular anymore.
People still like up-tempo and fun songs like that.
I felt again that people like up-tempo and fun songs like that.
I felt it again.
I like it too.
It's great.Sounds good.
What do you recommend?
But it's a bit like Western music.
I think everyone would have a great sense of togetherness at a live performance, don't you?
It sounds fun. Also, I think it's the chorus of the song.
I wish everyone would say "Hey, what's going on?
I don't know...
I'm singing by myself, and I've only just come out, so of course I'll be doing live shows.
And of course, in August, only a limited number of people will be able to see the mini live because of the lottery, so I hope we can do it again later.
I hope we can develop the song together.
So thank you very much, Ineine, and congratulations!
I wonder if I'm doing the right thing?
Thank you, Misaki!
Hina-chan, congratulations on your solo debut!
I can't stop getting excited every time I hear your wonderful news.
I'm so happy every day. Thank you so much for everything.
It's been a hot day here and there, so please take care of yourself.
I hope you have a great summer!
I love you so much, Hina-chan!
Thank you, Misaki-chan.
Misaki-chan!
This is it! This is it! I love you so much!
Is there a Misaki-chan? Misaki?
She's always here.
It's been really, really murder hot lately.
It's really hard to just walk around.
Isn't it hot, guys? It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm really sweating, I think I'm the only one.
I might be the only one in the world sweating.
Thank you, Misaki. Congratulations.
I'm the only one with a lot of sweat on my face.
Everyone who becomes a Toris has a beautiful face, and it looks cool.
I know it's hot, but you look cool.
I'm sure you're sweating that much.
But they're not sweating so much that they melt like I am.He's not sweating so much that he melts like I do.
Why do you think that is?
I don't know, maybe it's my metabolism.
I'm scared.
I don't go out and sweat.
I'm already sweating in the house with the air conditioning on.
And you're sweating, and then you step out and you're outside.
It's just too much. It's annoying.
I wish you wouldn't do that.
I think it's going to be hot for another month or so.
It's going to be hot in September anyway.
I'm scared.
Ho, who's next?
Thank you very much, Bal-kun, Bal-kun.
It's been a month since my debut, and I'm very happy to see that Hinata Kashiwagi is becoming more and more established, with more FC's, more goods, and so much media and content that it's hard to keep up with it all.
But what makes me happiest is the moment when I hear Hinata's music on my player while I'm commuting to work, and I know that my ears were not mistaken.
Thank you, I will be waiting for the next view. Looking forward to the next view.
What a nice comment!
What? Who is that? Is that you, Mr. Baru?
Open up.
What?
I was listening to myself.
Wow, thanks.
I'll do my best not to make a mistake.
Hey, Val.
All the good comments, all the good comments. What's going on? When did you guys grow up?
Why is that?
I can't say something like this in front of someone I like.
I can only say I like him.
We'll talk about it later.
Thank you, Mr. Burr.
Your ears are not wrong.
There's no mistake. I'm going to keep on singing, I'm going to keep on singing, I'm going to keep on doing my best.
Thank you, Mr. Baru.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, there he is, Mr. Baru.Oh, oh, there he is, Val.
I knew I saw you.
He's not in front of me, so I can tell you.
That's what Ano says.
Even if it's not right in front of you...
Even if he's writing a letter...
I'd be like, "What?
I wonder if it's okay.
I'm a bit of a nerd myself.
I can't get it off.
It looks like it's coming off.
Here!
[If you answered the question, please leave your answer in the comments section.
Mayana? Mayana?
Mayana? Is that correct?
Good evening, Hinata.
What is it? Bugs are here.
Did it smell good?
Maybe it smells good.
Good evening, sunshine.
I love you, Hinata-chan.
Especially your singing voice and your smile.
Love your cuteness!
And from.VTU. is great to get into the groove!
Of course, all the songs are great!
Hinatachan has always been my dream!
Thank you for always giving me so much energy!
I will continue to support you a lot!
Deliver VicLoveoo!
I love you so much!
Love you so much!
It's reaching me so much!
Big love is reaching so far!
Then you're a BIG LOVE BIG LOVE BIG LOVE
I'll put a heart.
I'll put something like this.I'm going to do this.
I mean...
I mean, this is the one I put at the top.
Thank you.
Hey... hey... hey... hey... hello...
Hey, hey, hey... bugs.
I get so many of these little buggers.
Did I smell that good?
You know what?
Will you stop coming when I'm writing?
I really don't think anyone can see them.
I'm the only one who can see them.
I know you're here.
You're here, aren't you?
Mayana!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's summer. Insects come here all the time.
Thank you, Ten-chan.
Thank you, Ten-chan. I've been in love with Hinachan for 10 years now.
That's a long time.
I was in junior high school, but now I'm in my fourth year of college. I love Hinachan more and more as time goes by.
Hinachan's voice has saved my life many times.
I'm so happy to be able to see you singing again.
I'll always support you anytime. Thank you very much, Ten-chan.
Ten years, that's a long time.
In your fourth year of college?
Hmm.
Huh? I just did that.
Are you writing your signature? Mr. Mae-Anon? Are you writing?
You've turned into a sibling, Ten-chan.
It makes me happy to hear you say you're someone I admire.
I wonder if you can handle it.
But it was a dream of mine, too.
I do what I do because I admire you. I do what I do because I admire others.
I want to be the kind of person people admire. I've been doing this for a long time, so I'm very grateful.I'm also grateful that I've always wanted to be the kind of person that people admire. I've been doing this for a long time, so I really appreciate it.
Thank you, Tenchan, and congratulations!
Oops.
Everyone's comments are... falling off!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Next, Kouhei-kun
Thank you, Kouhei-kun!
Congratulations on your solo debut!
I listen to your songs every day because they are full of so much charm!
They give me courage when I'm going through a hard time or when I have to work hard.
I have many difficulties as a new member of society.
but your songs help me to get over it every day.
I hope to see more of you in the future.
I will continue to listen to your voice and your hard work, which gives me courage and makes me want to do my best.
Please take care of yourself and do your best. Thank you, Benihira-kun.
I'm glad to hear you're a new member of society.
It's difficult, isn't it?
But still, you have to do your best.
But if it's really hard...
You have to have the courage to run away.
But you say you're doing your best... so I'm going to support you.
Thank you, KOUHEI Congratulations on your new job!
Don't overdo it. Go at your own pace.
Next up...
Okay, everyone.
Come on, come on, come on!
Ao-chan!
This is Ao-chan with lowercase letters.
Congratulations on your solo debut, Hina-chan!
Thank you.
I'm getting married soon.
I'm not sure which Hina-chan solo song to play.
Do you have any recommendations?
I'm listening to a lot now, and I'll listen to a lot more in the future.
Wedding
Congratulations!Congratulations!
Oh, my song!
I wonder if there's a song suitable for a wedding.
Hey.
But yeah.
But...
Wait a minute.
Uh...
Those days.
Wait a minute. No.
Those days is a little different.
Here you go, Mix.
It's a little bit of heartbreak mixed in... but...
Bloom.
Rust, Bloom, a tale of two people in bloom.
Let's go with "Bloom" Let's go with "Bloom
Bloom. Bloom.
Bloom, Bloom, Bloom, Bloom.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Practice... oh, I'm gonna sing it.
Too up-tempo for you? But it's good, isn't it?
There's a great lyric in the chorus.
Oh, Mi-chan!
You're a jack-of-all-trades.
Hmph, hmph, hmph, hmph...
I found a versatile song.
Over here
Ao-chan
Congratulations, Ao!
Have fun at the wedding.
Bloom it up.
By all means.
If you don't mind, anything.
Hmph.Huh.
Let's go next time.
7-chan. Thank you, 7-chan.
Hina-chan's singing voice and smile always cheers me up.
It's your voice that makes me laugh when I want to laugh and cry when I want to cry.
I'm so happy to witness your solo debut!
I will continue to support you.
Thank you, 7-chan.
You make me laugh when I want to laugh, but you also make me cry when I want to cry.
You mean you make me cry in a good way?
Yes, I am.
Is that Nana-chan?
Nana.
Oh, it says it's not me.
I thought you were that Nana.
But it turns out you're the wrong Nana.
But congratulations, Nana!
Here you go!
I haven't written many pages now.
Maybe I'll write more.
Saku-chan!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your release from here!
Starting with the exciting music from bow to toe
there is a sense of nostalgia
an emotional line that makes you feel determined
I want to close my eyes and picture the scene and listen to
those days
colorful and bouncy bloom
There is bitterness and frustration
I move forward with hope for the future
That's what Lunix is all about
It's really like a movie, the best EP ever, and I can't wait to do it with everyone.
And the cute ending is Saku-chan!
Thank you so much!Thank you very much.
Saku-chan, you're amazing! What a nuisance!
Thank you very much. I can't wait to do it.
Saku-chan
Thank you, Saku-chan!
I'll sing!
I love music!
Takayuki
Takayuki-kun, I'm sorry.
If you move the box, I'll move it
All these things I don't understand...
You've been out for a while now, haven't you?
I thought I was hiding them.
Oh well.
There was still my cell phone, café au lait, and lipstick.
Sorry, Takayuki-kun.
Thank you for the guess, Nata Kashiwagi!
I listen to the EP every day and it gives me energy!
I'm really looking forward to the live concerts you're going to hold in the future!
My dream is to continue to sing on stage!
Please let me continue to support you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for applying too!
Takayuki
Taka
Yoo
Ki-kun
Somehow the bugs have disappeared.
Maybe they went home.
I'm going to work a little harder on the live show.
Please keep up the good work! Thank you, Takayuki!
That was Takayuki.
Come on, Den!
Thank you, Suzu.
Good morning.
Hello, good evening.Hello and good evening.
Congratulations on your debut and EP release.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for all your hard work in the promotional activities from your debut to the release of the EP.
I was happy to hear Hinata Kashiwagi's voice every day.
Also, your Twitter timeline was very lively,
I looked forward to seeing it every day.
I am very happy to be able to support Hinata Kashiwagi every day.
I look forward to seeing more activities at Hinata Kashiwagi's pace in the future. Thank you very much.
Why does everyone call me Hinata Kashiwagi by my full name? I always wondered.
I wonder why Twitter has changed to Kashiwagi Hinata-san.
I wonder why.
Thank you, Suzu-chan.
I'll try my best again.
I'll work hard at Hinata-chan's pace. Thank you, Suzu-chan.
Kashiwagi Hinata-san is Kashiwagi Hinata-san's treasure.
I respect you because you're precious.
Hee.
Hehe.
Thank you.
Kashiwagi Hinata-san
Kashiwagi Hinata-san, I'll do my best.
Shibi-chan
Thank you.
Big newcomer, Ms. Hinata Kashiwagi.
Congratulations on your solo debut. Thank you.
Today's calendar and FC commentary, your debut as a singer, in your own way, Hinata.
Thank you for moving forward while thinking of your fans.
And listening to the thoughts you've put into these 5 new songs, I'm sure you'll cherish what you've done so far.
I want to support Hinachan as she takes a new step forward.
The latest Hinata Kashiwagi is the strongest Hinata Kashiwagi.
Hey, I have to work hard too, since everyone is cheering for me.
Kashiwa-chan.
More.
The circle of support is like a swallow.
Yakult fanYakult fan
Shibi-chan, thank you.
You've become Mr. Nata Kashiwagi, already.
I'm not Mr. Kashiwagi anymore.
He's going away.
Just one shuffle
Oh! That's him!
Ami!
Congratulations on your solo debut! Personally, I love Bloom so much! Please sing!
I can't sing! Take care of yourself, it's hot every day! Thank you!
Bloom is so popular! It's amazing!
Sorry about the song, I can't sing it here.
I can't sing it here, but I will sing it live.
We're talking about doing a live show.
Please come and listen to us then!
We'll definitely do it, Bloom!
We don't have any songs.
We have to do it.
Thank you, Ami-chan!
Oh, it's already been 30 minutes. That was fast.
Thank you, Marina. Congratulations on your debut.
I'm going to work listening to you from here. I'm so happy to hear your voice so soon. Keep up the good work at Hinata's pace.
I'll always support you no matter what your pace is. Thank you. My nose is suddenly itchy.
I wonder if I've got a bug in my nose.
I don't think so. There were no bugs.
My nose is suddenly itchy. Stop it!
Marina!
Marina.
Ta-da!
I'm kind of quiet when I'm writing.
This is it.
I don't know...
I knew it.
The surprise chair...
They're all listening to it.
Going to work...You know, going to work.
You know, riding the train and...
I'm so grateful that you're doing math for me.
Marina.
Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
Should I go faster?
Slow?
Normal?
That's good?
That's the pace.
You want to talk a lot?
My feet?
You don't know?
Are you okay?
I'm a little confused.
Thank you, Machi-chan.
Congratulations to Hinata Kashiwagi on her major label debut.
I love Hinata Kashiwagi the best, I love her so much, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's nice in the morning, isn't it?
It's like the beginning.
Oh! Machi-chan!
Thank you! Machi! Thank you!
Congratulations! We'll eat a lot of delicious food!
Now, wait a minute, inside.
Ho!
Ms. Nona
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your solo debut, Hina-chan!
It makes me so happy to think that I'll be able to hear more of your singing voice in the future.
Please keep up the good work at your own pace, Hina-chan!
I'll always support you.
Thank you for your love!
Ms. NonaNonasan.
Well, yes, now that I'm on my own...
I have to play more and more songs
more and more songs
I'll do my best.
I'll work at your pace, Hina-chan.
Good luck, Nona!
Thank you. Congratulations.
The background music has changed to NEXT2.
Which one?
This one.
Thank you, Tomomo.
Thank you for your always wonderful singing voice.
It's nice to meet you too, solo singer Hinata-san.
Your wonderful debut is going beyond my imagination, and I am getting more and more excited.
Please keep on singing in the face of the sun forever.
By the way, Zoes Days is my favorite song on this EP. I like all of them, so thank you Tomomo-san.
Zoes Days was also quite popular. I mean, all of them.
Everyone told me they liked it.
I've heard so many different impressions.
Everyone tweeted about it, so I'm very grateful.
I'm grateful for that.
Souls'Days is a great song.
I never thought I would sing that song.
I never thought the day would come when I would sing that song. Me too.
I'm glad I got to sing it.
Thank you. Tomomo-san.
Ah, there's Tomomo-san.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Sawa-chan.
Congratulations on your solo debut, Hina-chan!
I love Hina-chan's singing voice and smiling face!
Thank you for always making me happy.
I'm going to see you a lot more in the future. I love you so much!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy.I'm so happy for you.
Sara-chan!
I'll do my best so that you can come to see me a lot more in the future.
Thank you, Sawa-chan!
Oh!
Luka-chan!
Thank you very much.
Good evening, Hina-chan.
Congratulations on your solo debut!
I can't wait to hear my favorite Hina-chan's voice
I'm so happy to hear your voice again.
I'm really happy to hear your voice again.
Thank you very much.
I have a quick question.
Is there anything you try to do on a daily basis?
Like Hina-chan
I would love to know your secret to enjoy your daily life like you do.
I'd love to know!
Last but not least, I'm looking forward to hearing more of your music! Take care of yourself, Hina-chan, and thank you for loving me.
What do you keep in mind on a daily basis?
I don't really think about it.
You see the bugs, right?
Bugs, right?
What do you try to do on a daily basis?
I want to live a stable and peaceful life.
If I feel like I can't do something, I'll stop. If I feel like I can do something, I'll do it.
I try not to make it hard on myself.
I don't know. It's different from saying I don't want to be hard on myself.
I want to have a good time.
I guess it all comes out in my clothes.
Even if I wear black, I rarely wear black.
I don't wear black, but I definitely want to put color in something.
That's the thing... my mood is different.
I wear what I want to wear.
Wear what you want to wear? Yes.
There's been a lot of that lately, you know? I don't know...I don't know, there's been a lot of that lately, haven't there? I don't know...
You know, the problem of looking good and not looking good.
I don't know...
What about the bone structure?
or "blue-bone" or "yellow-bone"...
Of course, there may be such things.
But if you can't wear what you like, it's the end of you.
Yeah, I don't really care about that.
I want to wear what I like, eat what I like.
I want to spend my time as I like.
Thank you, Luka!
I don't want to live like that.
I don't want to live like that. I want to live at my own pace, and so does everyone else.
Like I said before, it takes courage to leave your home, and that's important.
Don't just run away from it. It's important to face it, too.
Oh! Thank you, Kaede!
Congratulations on your debut, Hina-chan!
My favorite song on the first EP is Bloom!
I knew it would be popular!
It's a very cheerful song, and I didn't think it was a love song.
So I guess it's a love song, so it's suitable for weddings.
I listen to it every day before I go to work to lift my spirits, and I'm looking forward to seeing more of you.
Take care of yourself and do your best.
Thank you very much.
There were girls who had fan names like Maya Mania, Mirelys...
Mirelees, right?
I don't know...
I want something.
I'm not sure myself.
I'm not sure if it's something I should decide on.
I don't know if it's something you want me to decide.
I don't know.
There may be people who just like the songs.
But I don't want them to feel like they have to call me by my fan name, so I'm not sure.
What do you think?
What do you think?What do you think?
I don't think it has to be.
Yeah, so...
It would be nice if we had one.
But I don't care if it's a fan club.
The name's on pace.
Whatever.
I'm doing it at the pace of the sun.
so I thought it would be nice if there was something like that.
I thought it would be nice to have something like that.
I don't want my fans to think
I don't think it's necessary to say
I don't think it's necessary to make
I don't think I have to make
I don't have one at the moment.
I don't have any plans to make one.
I don't know if there will be a time when I really need something, but I'll think about it if there is something.
I don't know if I'll really need something someday, but I'll think about it if something comes up.
Thank you very much, Kaeri!
Thank you!
Thank you, Ms. Isaki! Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your solo debut.
They are all good songs, but personally
I personally like "emotional warfare" and "next you".
E~I'm looking forward to hearing them at the live performance.
I will continue to support you. I love you.
Thank you very much.
Emotional battle is, you know,
It's a great song.
Next you too.
They are all good songs, really.
Isaki-san.
Thank you very much.
I'll try my best to get everyone to listen to them at the concert soon.
Thank you, Saki.
Thank you, Arisa.Arisa-chan Thank you very much!
Hina-chan I especially like Bloom and listen to it every day!
I hope you will make an easy dance at the chorus someday!
I will continue to support you.
Thank you for always cheering me up!
Thank you very much.
Bloom.
How about it? How about it?
It's an easy dance.
No? No? What is it?
What is it? Let me think.
I'm just imagining, Bloom, that it's a real towel-chomping song.
That's it! Isn't that good?
Bloom's really popular. Maybe. I'd like to throw in the towel.
We're all in front here.
But if it's for TikTok, I'll do my best to think of something.
Thank you, Arisakura!
I'd like to make towels and other goods.
Someday.
I'll have to do a live show.
I won't write songs. Just towels.
Only Saki towels. Thank you, John.
Congratulations to Nata Kashiwagi on her solo debut single from about you and her first EP from here!
And thank you very much for your hard work on the campaign throughout Japan!
I am very happy to hear 5 songs by Kazuha Kashiwagi even though it's only been 6 months since his graduation.
Thank you for continuing your activities as a solo artist. Please let me continue to support you.
So thank you very much.
Well, I went to many places for the release of the EP, and it was a lot of fun.
It's been a while since I've been to so many places.
Ms. Jyon, Ms. Jyon
Hey, I am very happy to have 5 songs of my own in about 6 months.
I'm still working hard.
Thank you, John.
I'm singing, I'm singing.
I'm singing.
Oh, there he is.Oh, there was Mr. John.
Well, thank you very much, Yuya.
Masu.
It's been a while since I've been called boss.
Congratulations on your solo debut, boss. Thank you very much.
Your dance was so sharp, the song was up-tempo, and it was cool and very Hinata-like.
Please keep up the good work and don't overdo it. So, thank you very much.
Hey, boss, you should make your boss debut.
Yuya.
Subscribe to our channel!
Great. I wonder if everyone still calls me boss.
Thank you, Yuya. I'll do my best. Congratulations.
Thank you, Moe-chan!
Congratulations on your solo debut! All the songs on the EP, from here on out, are really wonderful.
When I heard them for the first time, I was filled with various feelings. I'm really looking forward to the live concert!
Thank you for always giving me so much happiness and energy.
I hope you keep smiling and having fun with your face.
I'll be happy if you continue to take care of yourself and your feelings as well as your body.
I will always support you.
Mikurabu!
Thank you, Moe-chan!
You say, "Take care of your feelings.
You too, Moe-chan, treasure your feelings!
I'm sure your feelings are really important.
I've been thinking about it again recently.
To communicate, to convey...
Thank you, Moe!
MIKURABU
Well...
Oh, there it is. Kanata-chan. Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your solo debut.
I am truly happy to see Kashiwagi Hinata-san singing and dancing and shining again.
Meeting Kashiwagi Hinata-san is the greatest honor in my life.
It is our encouragement to see Hinata-san's smile from now on.
I really love you. Thank you very much.
Oh no, I can't get used to calling myself Kashiwagi Hinata-san anymore.Oh no, I can't get used to calling myself Kashiwagi Hinata-san anymore.
Kanata-chan, one letter different from mine.
Kanata-chan.
I will continue to do my best to bring you smiles.
Thank you, Kanata-chan.
Last one?
You're early! Already the last one!
Let's see who's on it.
We got a lot of entries.
A lot of people have applied, so...
It's a big turnout.
What should we do?
I don't know.
I'll take this one.
Oh, I got two.
This one. Ready?
Who's that?
Shiho.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your solo debut.
I am very happy to hear your singing voice from now on.
I will continue to support you so that you will be able to spend a wonderful life without overworking your health.
Thank you very much.
The last one was Shiho-chan.
This time, everyone's name is signed and dated.
The name of the person whose name will be drawn in this drawing.
The last one was Shiho-chan.
Thank you very much.
We received many entries from both men and women.
Thank you, Shiho.
Congratulations. You're the last one.
Okay, so...
The signing is over.
Congratulations to the winners.
And, um...And, uh...
I didn't win. Unfortunately, I didn't win.
But, everyone who bought the cheki...
Thank you very much.
Well, it's almost the end of the show...
Well, I have an announcement.
Can I go? Go ahead.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to interrupt.
An announcement.
Yes, I have an announcement.
I have a fan club called "On Pace", which has been rented out.
I'm happy to announce that our first fan club event is coming up!
Here you go! Thank you for waiting!
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey, everyone!
Did people say we're getting married? I'm not getting married. I'm not announcing my marriage here.
We'll be holding a fan club event. I'd like to tell you the date. It's at a certain place in Tokyo.
It's at a certain place in Tokyo, but I'll let you know the date ahead of time.
It will be on Sunday, October 15, 2023.
I'll be making this announcement every time I get married or something.
I don't know why.
I haven't even been picked up by Bunshun or anything.
I didn't get it.
But everyone says it's true and it's going to be in the next issue of a weekly magazine.
It's like a weekly magazine, right? A weekly magazine.
I want to be in a weekly magazine about peace.
I'd like to be in a weekly about peace, like eating something, or buying a lot of beer, or something like that.
I'd like to be photographed coming out of a low-cost store.
I'd like to be photographed like that, so I'll do my best to be photographed like that.
Yes, I'm going to hold a fan club event on Sunday, October 15th at a place in Tokyo to prevent the event from happening.
The title of the event is Hinata's Banquet.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I don't know what we're going to do.
I don't know what we're going to do... but we'd like to keep it really loose.
I've been in groups before... where things are too tight.
But since I'm alone, I can't do anything.I mean, it's a fanclub image, so I'm supposed to do something interesting, but since I'm alone, I can't do anything.
No songs? Then let's sing other people's songs at the banquet.
That's right, so I've been thinking about it a little bit.
So maybe I'll ask everyone to sing, and maybe I'll give the microphone to someone and ask them to sing, so everyone just prepare your voice, and I'll see you in about three months.
So I'd like to do a lot of things, and we can all have fun, and we can all sing, and we can all get excited, and we can laugh, and we can all have fun, and we can all have fun.
I'd like to have a lot of fun with everyone, and since it's a fan club members-only event, it'll be more fun.
I hope it will be a fun event where people can enjoy themselves more deeply with me.
I'm still a little nervous about doing it by myself, but I think I can do it with everyone else,
I am still a little nervous about doing it alone, but I am sure I can do it with everyone's help.
I hope you are looking forward to it. I will announce the tickets and other details on the website or something like that.
Please wait for more details.
I was asked, "Are you Jokichiji? I was told, "Are you JOKIJI?
I said, "That's fine. It's fine, isn't it?
I'll tell you about that later.
I'll tell you what I'm bringing.
I was wondering if my hoodie would arrive before the FC event. I'll do my best.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do. I'm going to wear it. That's why I want to wear it.
Why, yes, that's why they call it a banquet,
But, you know, there's absolutely no drinking culture or anything like that. If I do that, I'll get fired.
I'll be fired from my job for sure. I'll get fired.
I'll go there. I'm not going to do that. There are people who can't drink, underage people, students, and so on,
I hope this will be an event where everyone can enjoy themselves and have a good time.
I hope it will be an event where everyone can have a good time together. That's all I have to say.
Anything else you want to say? Oh, it's my hair. Hair, hair. If you're wondering why I cut it, I really just wanted to cut it.
Seriously, I wanted to cut it, but I wanted to make it shorter, but I didn't know what to do.
When I was thinking about how short I wanted to cut it, I decided to go to my house.
I love Ryoko Yonekura, and I was a member of her fan club. I love Ryoko Yonekura, and I was a member of her fan club.
It's been on display for a long time now, and the month of July, Yone-san's calendar was around this time.
I thought, "Hey, I want to hear about it around this time," and, "Hey, I want to hear about it around this time.
I told you about the fan club event yesterday.
Yesterday, I was on some kind of thread or something, and I was talking about how I'm geeking out, how I'm enjoying my geek life to the fullest, like a nerd.
I was at MAX's fan club event yesterday, and I love MAX, and I went to MAX's fan club event.
So I went to MAX's fan club event.
We went bowling, which was a lot of fun.
And I like Meena. Her hair is like...
You know how she wears her hair short-cut and blonde like that? So...You know, with the short cut and the blonde hair? And...
There's a song called "Parthenon," and Mina's hair was about this length at the time.
So I thought I had no choice but to cut it to this length, and I wanted to cut it that way.
That's why...
So I went to a fan club event with the song cut.
And then I went to the fan club event, and Meena-san kissed me, and I was like, "What?
So, at first, how many people were in the fan club?
I won a prize in a fan club that only takes about 100 people.
You mean? But I also said hi to her once... when I was in another group.
We've met.
So I wasn't sure if it'd be okay if I went.
I was wondering if it'd be okay if I went, but then he came up to me, and he said, "You know, it's bowling, so there's lanes like this.
I can't tell you the details, but he came up to me and said...
And then one time I was like, "Ah! And I was like...
And then I was like, "Ah! Then maybe he noticed me. Maybe he noticed me.
I just gave him a quick speech.
And then later, when the bowling tournament started...
He came over and said, "Hey...
Why are you here? Like...
Why did you come? Like...
Why are you in the fan club? He was like, "I'm sorry.
I said, "I'm sorry, I just like you and I'm a member of your fan club.
He said he was going to go bowling with you guys.
Fan club events.
I've never been to a fan club event before.
I said, "I just wanted to go to a MAX event.
I said, "I'm here.
And then...
He said he recognized me right away.
He was following me on Instagram.
And I was like, "I'm following you, too.
I was like...
I saw on your Instagram that you got a haircut.
She said she recognized me right away.
I was so nervous.
I was like, "Oh, I'm sorry.Oh, like, sorry.
That's all I could say.
I'm going to enjoy it.
And there were all kinds of examples.
Just when I was about to pitch.
I was just about to pitch.
I was bowling with a bunch of fans who were really nice to me, and I was bowling with a bunch of fans who were really nice to me.
I was bowling with fans I've never met before.
Hmmm...
Hmmm.
Yeah, so...
And as we were doing it, all the members were going around.
And then Nana noticed you, too.
Yes, you came? Thank you.
And then, just as I was doing something...
And just as I was about to throw the ball, you came again.
And I said, "Oh, it's you, Nana-chan.
I told her to go for it, and she did.
I was like, "I want to show them how good I am.
I was like, "I want to show them how good I am! How embarrassing!
I threw it.
I thought I had a great shot at the purse, but it was a 9-pin.
I was like, "Oh my God, I'm so embarrassed to go back in there.
You guys had been doing this for a long time.
Ina-chan told me that if I beat her by 1 pin and got a spare
I'll give you a high-five!
I was like, "Go get the spare! Go! Ai! I thought.
I was already talking to the ball the whole time. I was like, "You've got to go for that pin.
Just go... just go straight.
I can't! I successfully high-fived Mirina and got the spare!
And then at night, there was Yone's insta-live.
Yone's fan club had an insta-live, so it was a really fulfilling
It was a good night. It was such a fulfilling one!
And I'm also going to MAX's live in December as a member of his fan club!
I wrote a letter to MAX yesterday.
I wrote a letter to MAX yesterday and gave it to the staff.I wrote a letter and gave it to the staff.
But I couldn't write anything at all.
It's always been...
There's no group that cool now, right?
Four girls.
"Fans are cool.
And YouTube.
Moto-chan and Sabu-chan were there.
It's like Malaysia, Malaysia.
I'll try to work with them someday.
I'll try my best to work with you someday.
something like that.
But fans
It's kind of weird.
It was a letter set.
You wrote on a bread letter set.
I just wanted to make sure it was okay.
Yeah, it's from MAX's Jogei Channel... and...
Bon-bon-bon MAX the Bomb.
I was so happy to see him, and I wanted to see him dance more.
I wanted to see MAX dancing even more, so I just watched MAX THE BOMB's "Fixed Point Dance.
I was up at 4:00 a.m. last night watching MAX the Bomb.
I even stopped by in the morning.
It was like I was watching until 4 in the morning.
The most recent emergency report was yesterday.
I'm sorry, it's just too much already.
But maybe that's why he's on MAX's definition channel.
I've been watching youtube. Maybe he's on it.
What? I hope so.
I want to be in it.
I was so happy to be able to go to someone's fan club event like this.
I was so happy.
Okay, I'll end now.
I had so much fun at the fan club event, so I'm going to do it too.
I wanted to say that I had a great time at the fan club event, so I'm going to do it too, so let's all have fun together.
Well, I've finished signing the papers...Yes, well, now that the signing is over, I'm going home.
I'm going home.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you to the 527 people who listened to me.
It was fun. You were all so cute.
You were all so cute. You were all so cute.
Thank you very much. That's it.
Okay, everyone be careful.
I'll let you all know if I do anything nerdy like this.
In the meantime, I have to take care of myself.
I have a concert in August. August 12, 13.
I'll be working hard for that, too.
And after that, there will be various events for the fan club.
I will do my best to keep working on my activities.
I will do my best to keep you all informed of various things.
I hope you are all looking forward to it.
Yes, today is the online signing to commemorate my solo debut.
I'll leave the archive here with a deadline.
If you were invited to the event but couldn't see it, please let me know.
If you were invited but couldn't see it, you don't know.
If you couldn't see it because you didn't know if you didn't see it
I hope you will watch it later and, uh, do it!
Well, I am glad that I could talk with you all for just a little over an hour today, and I am very happy that we could have this conversation together. Thank you very much.
Today is Sunday! Tomorrow is Monday! I don't know if you are working, going to school, or on summer break from school. I don't know, but let's all do our best!
Thank you! Bye!
Thank you for watching!